{
    "id": "1c74c717ada843e895e9a321188f449c",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He accused me …………………….. stealing his money.",
            "description": "We accuse somebody of something",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am afraid ………………………… spiders.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you agree …………………………… his decision to quit?",
            "description": "You agree with a person, opinion or policy.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We agree …………………………. most things.",
            "description": "We agree about a subject of discussion.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know why he is angry ………………………….. me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am anxious ……………………………. my exam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "about",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We are all anxious ………………………….. an end to this conflict.",
            "description": "Anxious for means eager to have.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "about",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They apologized …………………………… the old lady.",
            "description": "Apologize to somebody for something",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We arrived …………………………….. New York in the afternoon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is quite good …………………………… mind reading.",
            "description": "We say good at or bad at. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t believe …………………………. ghosts or fairies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Those vases belong ………………………………. that shelf.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "to",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}